bookrags.com 2014-11-05

# Privacy Policy : Customer Service

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to BookRags. Please read the following to learn about BookRags' commitment to maintaining your privacy.

**Registration**

BookRags may, from time to time send you information about your BookRags account. BookRags collects personally identifiable information that you provide to us if you register on the BookRags website, such as your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address. If you are a paying member at BookRags, this also includes your credit card and related information.

BookRags may use personally identifiable information, without limitation, to email you updates on your service, general product updates, notices regarding material changes to the site policies, subscription updates and changes, customer service issues, and special offers from BookRags or its partners or affiliates.

You may choose at any time to opt out of receiving some or all of these communications. To change your settings, please visit "Privacy Settings" under your [My BookRags](https://www.bookrags.com/qa/myaccount.php) page. You can also select 'unsubscribe' from emails that you receive from BookRags.

Because some communications are important to ensure that we provide our users with the highest quality of service, our members cannot opt out of email contact on changes in site policies, customer support services, or any other issues deemed by BookRags to be important to communicate.

BookRags uses some of your personal information in accordance with the Terms of Service. We may also engage a co-registration program with our partners and we will be able to communicate with you and use demographic data about you. To change your settings, please visit "Privacy Settings" under your [My BookRags](https://www.bookrags.com/qa/myaccount.php) page.

We also reserve the right to assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your personally identifiable information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of all or substantially all of our assets.

**Links to Other Sites**

BookRags is not responsible for the privacy policies of other web sites it is linked to.

**Information Collection and Use**

BookRags automatically receives and records information on our server logs, including IP addresses and browser specifics. This information is used by BookRags to examine our market penetration and demographics. BookRags also reserves the right to anonymously track and report activity within our website and applications whether online or mobile.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

BookRags also works with third parties to help us understand how people use our web site and to provide functionalities such as e-mail distribution, ad serving and user surveys. These companies may also use cookies or other tracking technologies, such as web beacons, which are similar in function to cookies, allowing them to determine when users have reached particular web pages on the BookRags website. For more information on cookies, visit: <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>.

**Security**

If you do register, your information is kept safely and securely within BookRags. If you have any specific concerns or questions, please don't hesitate to [contact us](http://bookrags.zendesk.com/tickets/new). We are very concerned about the security of customer data. We store your information securely, using industry-compliant encryption technology.

**Age Policy**

BookRags is a service for students over the age of 13 years old. If you are younger than 13, you are not permitted to register on BookRags.com.        

**Q &A and Homework Help**

All information disclosed on the Q&A/Homework Help by the user is public information. Users should have a level of awareness when posting on the Q&A/Homework Help. Any views expressed in the BookRags Q&A/Homework Help are not necessarily the views of BookRags or its staff.

**Advertising**

 We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these company, please visit the Consumer Choice page. (link to <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/>)

 BookRags has partnered with Glam Media Inc. for display advertising. You may contact Glam at their website (link to <http://www.glammedia.com/contact_us/index.php>) Glam, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve behaviorally targeted advertisements based on your Internet usage. To learn more about Glam's commitment to consumer choice and privacy please visit their [Privacy and Security Policy](http://www.glammedia.com/about_glam/legal/privacy.php). (link to <http://www.glammedia.com/about_glam/legal/privacy.php>)

 Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on BookRags.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to BookRags and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Privacy Policy Changes**

BookRags will make changes to this privacy policy from time to time.

If you have any additional questions, please [contact us](http://bookrags.zendesk.com/tickets/new) at:

BookRags, Inc.

2025 1st Ave, Suite 270

Seattle, WA 98121
